Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 126. A sermon on Algeria, 1992; 1 (Box 126)
  Side B: The first speaker on side A gives another sermon in which he talks about Algeria and calls for supporting Algeria as it is a Muslim country. He speaks about the Islamic Salvation Front in Algeria and how its members were exposed to harassments, arrests, and confiscation of property. He speaks about a report from the US Department of Defense which contains information about directing nuclear warheads to many third world countries. He speaks about a speech of the former Tunisian president in which he announces the war against t the Islamic revival.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 45:13 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:06 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 2:44 ?????
  ?? 2:45 ??? 41:30 ??????? ????? ?? ???? ??????? ????????? ?? ??????? ??? ????? ??????? ?? ?? ????????? ??????????? ? ????? ??? ?????? ? ???? ?????? ?????? ??? ??????. ???? ???? ???? ?? ??? ?? ????? ????? ????????? ??? ????? ??????? ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ?????????
  ?? 41:31 ??? ????? ????? ????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ??? ????? ???? ?? ???????? ??????? ?????? ???????? ??? ??????? ???????? ??????????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ??????? ????? ?? ????? ????? ???? ???? ???? ????? ???? ?? ??????? ?????? ????? ???? ??????? ????? ??? ????. ????? ?? ???? ??????? ???????? ??? ????? ?? ?? ???????? ???????? ??????? ??????????. ????? ?? ????? ?????? ?????? ????????? ?? ????? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ??????. ????? ?? ???? ?????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??? ??? ?????? ?????? ?????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 127. A lecture on Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 127)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 45:22 min. Side B 45:27min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The tape starts with an introduction to the recording by al-taqwa? recordings; then the speaker gives a lecture on Jihad. He believes that Jihad is a legitimate imposition derived from the Qur?a?n and Hadith and it is valid until the Day of Resurrection. He speaks about the Muslim sect who is promised victory and believes it is the Sunnis who are responsible for Jihad and the promotion of virtue and the prevention of vice.
  Side B: Continuation of the same lecture on side A. The same speaker talks about the victorious sect. He mentions their distinguishing features and cites Hadiths. He answers various questions from the audience such as questions on al-Ba?th party and the victorious sect.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 45:22 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:27 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ???? ?????? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ?? ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ?????? ???? ???? ???? ??? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ??? ??? ???????. ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?????? ????? ??? ????? ???????? ??? ???????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ?? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??? ???????? ?? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ???? ?????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?????? ????? ?????? ????????? ??????? ???? ??????? ?????. ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ??? ????? ???????? ???????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 128. A lecture on women, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 128)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 29:35 min. Side B 29:38 min. Speaker: Sulayma?n ibn H?amad al-?Awdah. Place: Suadi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker gives a lecture on women. He speaks about the role of women at home and work. He believes that the house is a woman's natural place and that she should not go out without the consent of her husband. He cites verses from the Qur?a?n, Hadiths, and stories from the history of Islam on Muslim women. He narrates Hadith in which the Prophet allowed women to go out to do necessary things. The speaker believes in the necessity to separate men from women in educational institutions.
  Side B: Continuation of the same lecture on side A. The speaker criticizes Huda? Sha?ra?wi?'s statement on women's rights. He talks about the views of some Western thinkers on the negative sides of women's liberation in society. He reviews articles by Arab journalists, intellectuals, and media figures on the disadvantages of women's work.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 29:35 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:38 ?????. ???????: ?????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ??????. ????? ??? ????? ?? ???? ?????? ??????? ??? ??? ?????? ?? ?? ???? ?? ????? ??? ??????? ?????. ?????? ????? ?? ??????, ?????? ????. ???? ???? ???? ???? ??? ?????? ?????? ??????? ????? ???????. ????? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ?????? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??? ???????? ?? ????? ?????. ??????? ????? ???? ???? ?????? ?? ???? ??????. ????? ?? ???? ??? ???????? ???????? ?? ?????? ???? ?????? ?? ??????? ??????? ?????? ??????? ????????? ??????? ??? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 129. Reviewing aspects of jurisprudential books, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 129)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 46:04 min. Side B 46:00 min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  0:00 to 35:51 The tape starts with an introduction to the recorded lecture by "Uh?ud for media production and distribution". Then, a speaker starts a lecture in which he reviews chapters from "Tadhkirat al-sa?mi? wa-al-mutakallim fi? adab al-?a?lim wa-al-muta?allim" by Ibn Jama??ah. The book mainly addresses the relationship between the religious scholar or al-Shaykh and his student.
  35:52 to the end of side A, another recording for the same speaker in which he reviews chapters from "Za?d al-ma?a?d fi? hady khayr al-?iba?" by Ibn Qayyim al-Jawzi?yah. He reviews aspects of the book that explain some Hadiths.
  Side B: Continuation of the last lecture on side A. The same speaker reviews other chapters from the same book and some jurisprudential issues.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:04 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:00 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 35:51 ???? ????? ????? ?????? ???????? ??????? ?? ??? "???" ??????? ???????? ????????. ???? ????? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ?? ???? " ????? ?????? ???????? ?? ??? ?????? ????????" ???? ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????? ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ??????? ????? ?????
  ?? 35:52 ??? ????? ????? ????? ????? ??? ???? ??????? ?????? ??? ???? "??? ?????? ?? ??? ??? ??????" ???? ??? ???????. ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ???? ???? ????
  ????? ??????: ????? ???????? ??????? ?? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ?????? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ???? ??????? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 130. A sermon on the Iraqi invasion of Kuwait, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 130)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 131. Audio recording of a military operation, part of a sermon, and a recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 131)
  Comments: There is no side A. Side B 46:11 min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah.
  Side A: [Blank.]
  0:00 to 19:52 a recording of fire from various weapons with unclear sounds of people speaking through what appears to be a battle somewhere.
  19:53 to 29:05 A speaker answers different questions on jurisprudential issues.
  30:00 to the end of side B, a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat al-H?ujura?t verses 6-18, Qa?f verses 1-45, and al-Dha?riya?t verses 1-30.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ??? ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:11 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ??? ?????
  ????? ?????: ??? ?????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 19:52 ????? ???? ?????? ??? ?? ????? ?????? ? ????? ??? ????? ?????? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ??? ????? ???? ?? ???? ??
  ?? 19:53 ??? 29:05 ??????? ???? ?? ????? ????? ??????
  ?? 30:00 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 6 ??? 18 ????? ? ????? 1 ??? 45 ????? ???????? ????? 1 ??? 30
  - Preservation masters, 1
  - Use copies, 1
- Tape 132. A sermon on sybarites, 1990; 1 (Box 132)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 30:08 min. Side B 30:45 min. Speaker: Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker talks about the events of wars and instability in Palestine, Afghanistan and Lebanon, and then he talks about the Iraqi invasion of Kuwait and the consequences of this invasion on the Kuwaiti people. He concludes that the cause of a disaster experienced by any people is the negligence of people in their worship of God.
  Side B: Continuation of the same sermon on side A. The speaker talks about luxury and defines it as the exaggeration of enjoying graces which leads to disobedience of God. He speaks about the disadvantages of excessive luxury.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 30:08 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:45 ?????. ???????: ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ????? ?? ??????? ???? ??? ???????, ????????? ? ????? ?? ???? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ??????? ?? ???????? ??????? ?????? ??? ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ???? ??? ???????? ????? ??? ?? ??? ??????? ???? ??? ??? ?? ??? ?? ????? ????? ?? ????? ????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?????. ??????? ????? ?? ????? ??????? ???? ???????? ?? ?????? ?????? ????? ???? ??? ????? ???? ???? ?????. ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 133. A sermon on the causes of happiness, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 133)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 46:19 min. Side B 46:17 min. Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Speaker: Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker continues his sermon. He lists the causes of happiness. He answers questions from the audience about worship in Ramadan, envy, and other subjects.
  Side B: The speaker gives a sermon on the causes of happiness. He speaks about people's different views of happiness and searching for it and narrates stories related to this topic.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:19 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:17 ?????. ???? ?????? ??????. ???????: ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ??? ??????. ???? ????? ???????. ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ? ?????? ????
  ????? ??????: ??????? ???? ???? ?? ????? ???????. ????? ?? ???????? ????? ??????? ???????? ??????? ?????? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ???
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 134. Reviewing Hadiths on jurisprudential issues, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 134)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 46:30 min. Side B 40:01 min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah.
  Side A: The speaker reviews Hadiths on the permissibility of eating dead animals such as whales and insects like locusts. He reviews Hadiths from different narrators, in particular from Abu? Hurayrah.
  Side B: The same speaker reviews other Hadiths on animals from different narrators. He answers questions from the audience.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:30 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 40:01 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ????????? ??? ????? ???????? ??? ??????. ???? ???????? ?? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ???????? ???? ????? ??? ????? ?? ??????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ???? ?????? ????? ???? ?? ????????? ?? ???? ???????. ???? ?? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 135. A lecture on youth delinquency, 1990; 1 (Box 135)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 43:45 min. Side B 43:02 min. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The speaker gives a lecture about the causes of delinquency in youth and methods for their reformation. He offers tips to fathers on how to deal, care for, and strengthen the relationship with their children. He recommends that fathers follow up with their children and not leave them vulnerable to delinquency.
  Side B: The same speaker continues his lecture and advises mothers to follow up with their children and that siblings should pay attention to their younger siblings. He also directs his speech to teachers and Islamic preachers to contribute in educating youth and guiding them to commit to religion. He answers many questions from the audience.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 43:45 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:02 ?????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ?????? ???? ???????. ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ??????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?????? ??????? ??? ????? ?????? ????????? ???????? ???????? ???? ????? ???? ????????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ???? ??????? ????? ??????? ??? ???? ??????? ??????? ???? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?????. ???? ????? ???? ??? ???????? ??????? ?????????? ???????? ?? ????? ?????? ???????? ??? ???????? ??????. ???? ?? ????? ????? ?? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 136. A sermon on the sneaking whisperer, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 136)
  Comments: Recording quality is faint and there is background noise especially on side A but audio is intelligible. Side A 28:36 min. Side B 25:28 min. Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Speaker: The speaker is most likely Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah.
  Side A: The speaker continues his sermon on the sneaking whisperer that whispers in the hearts of mankind. He believes that the source of this whisperer is the devil and that the way to get rid of the devil's plots is commitment to religion.
  Side B: The speaker gives a sermon on the sneaking whisperer, the devil's plots, and types of satanic whisperers and how to resist them. He advises the audience to be cautious of the devil's machinations. He lists the physical and psychological symptoms of whisperers. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ????? ??????? ????? ????? ????? ???? ?? ????? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 28:36 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 25:28 ?????.???? ?????? ??????. ???????: ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ??? ??????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ????? ?? ???????. ??? ?? ???? ??????? ?? ??????? ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ??????? ?? ???????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ??????? ???? ???? ?? ???????, ??? ???????, ?????? ??????? ????????? ?????? ????????. ???? ????????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ????. ???? ??????? ??????? ???????? ???????. ????? ??????? ??????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 137. A sermon on war, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 137)
  Comments: Audio is intelligible. Side A 45:37 min. Side B 46:03 min. Speaker: Salma?n ibn Fahd al-?Awdah. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: The tape starts with an introduction to the recording by al-taqwa? recordings. The speaker gives a sermon on war. He speaks about invasions by Muslims (Islamic conquests). He criticizes the call for peace by the West and considers that war would be an option for Muslims in particular in their search for justice.
  0:00 to 41:56 The same speaker continues his sermon and talks about Jewish people as the most dangerous enemies of Muslims. He confirms that Muslims will face a promised war and a decisive battle with Jewish people and promises Muslims the victory in this battle.
  42:12 to the end of side B, A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Anfa?l verses 60-66.
  ?????????: ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 45:37 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:03 ?????. ???????: ????? ?? ??? ??????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ???? ?????? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ??????? ??????. ??????? ???? ?????? ?? ?????. ????? ?? ??????? ???? ??? ??? ???????? (???????? ?????????). ????? ?????? ??? ?????? ?? ??? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ???? ?????? ???????? ???????? ???? ????? ????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 41:56 ??? ??????? ???? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ???? ????? ???????? ????? ??? ???????? ??????? ????? ?????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ???? ???????? ?????? ?? ??? ???????
  ?? 42:12 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 60 ??? 66
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 138. Q&A session, 1990; 1 (Box 138)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 30:49 min. Side B 31:06 min. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: A speaker answers questions and speaks about inviting people to Jihad, the promotion of virtue and prevention of vice, teamwork, and supporting religious scholars and preachers. He strongly criticizes women's demonstrations in the city of Riyadh in Saudi Arabia that called for women's emancipation. He attacks the Consultative Assembly of Saudi Arabia and believes that it has been founded with American interference. He speaks about the Iraqi invasion of Kuwait.
  Side B: The same speaker on side A continues to answer questions about the position of Saudi press regarding women's demonstrations, accusing them of unbelief and violation of Islamic laws. He attacks the Iraqi and Syrian Ba?th parties and describes the two parties and both Saddam Hussein and H?a?fiz? al-Asad as infidels. He urges the audience to prevent any calls for liberation, especially for women.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 30:49 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:06 ?????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??????? ??????? ????? ?????. ????? ???? ??????? ???? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ???????? ????? ?????? ??????. ????? ???? ?????? ??????? ?????? ??? ????? ????? ??????. ????? ?? ???????? ??????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ?? ?????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?? ???? ??????? ???????? ?? ????????? ???????? ????? ??? ??????? ???????? ?????? ??????? ??????? ?????????. ????? ??? ????? ??????? ??????? ????? ???? ????? ????? ??????? ??????. ???? ??? ????? ??? ?? ???? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 139. Q&A session on Arabic and Islamic counties, Circa 1983-2000; 1 (Box 139)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. The language used is modern standard Arabic and Sha?mi? dialect. Side A 42:48 min. Side B 42:45 min. Place: Peshawar-Pakistan.
  Side A: A speaker talks about the Islamic countries and regimes and believes that there is no Islamic regime in the present time that fully applies Islamic law. He speaks about the future of Afghanistan and supports ?Abd al-Rashi?d Dostum as he imposes the Islamic laws. He considers it a duty to fight S?adda?m H?usayn and al-Ba?th party and wishes that the United States would attack al-Qadhdha?fi?. He mentions protests that took place in his country (Jordan).
  Side B: The same speaker continues and answers questions from the audience. He speaks about some of the laws in Islamic countries such as Saudi Arabia and Jordan and criticizes these laws because their conflict with the Islamic legislations such as banking laws. He commends the liberty of Muslims, the proliferation of mosques and the proselytizing of Islam in the United States. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 42:48 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 42:45 ?????. ????? ????????? ?? ??????? ?????? ??????? ???????. ??????: ??????- ???????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ????? ?? ????? ???????? ????????? ? ????? ???? ???? ???? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ????????? ???????. ????? ?? ?????? ????????? ?????? ????? ????? ??? ?????? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ????????? ????? ???? ??????? ?????????. ????? ?????? ???? ???? ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ???????. ????? ?? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ?? ???????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ???? ?????? ???????? ?? ????? ??????. ????? ?? ??? ???????? ?? ??????? ????????? ??? ???????? ??????? ???????? ???? ??????? ?? ??????? ????????? ??? ?????? ??????. ???? ??? ???? ?????? ??????? ??????? ??????? ??? ??????? ?? ???????? ???????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 140. Q&A session on apostasy, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 140)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. The language used is modern standard Arabic and Sha?mi? dialect. Side A 40:02 min. Side B 44:00 min.
  Side A: A speaker talks about the apostles throughout the history of Islam such as those who abstained from performing religious impositions such as prayers and alms giving (Zaka?t). He discusses the provisions of the Islamic legislation on these apostates. He discusses with the audience several religious obligations and the identification of apostates.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about those who abstain from the Islamic law (Shari??ah), for instance, he mentions that he considers anyone affiliated with the intelligence agency in his country (Jordan) is infidel. He reviews Ibn Taymi?yah's opinion in fighting the apostates. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ????? ????????? ?? ??????? ?????? ??????? ???????. ??? ????? ????? 40:02 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:00 ?????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ????? ?? ???????? ??????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?????? ??????? ?? ???? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ??????? ? ????? ??? ??????? ?? ????? ????????. ?????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ??? ?? ??????? ??????? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ???????? ???????? ????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ????? ?? ????? ???????? ?? ???????? ???????? ????????? ????? ??? ???? ?????? ????? ???????? ??? ????????? ?? ???? (??????). ?????? ??? ??? ????? ?? ????? ???????? ???????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 141. A sermon on faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 141)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 46:35 min. Side B 45:29 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon on faith, its meaning and legislative definition, its requirements, and its benefits. He cites verses from the Qur?a?n, Hadiths and books from Salafi? scholars about faith.
  0:00 to 28:00 The same speaker continues his sermon on faith. He reviews other resources from Salafi? scholars' books on faith. He speaks in more detail about the faith requirements.
  28:01 to the end of side B, Recitation from the Qur?a?n for Surat al-Insa?n verses 24-31, al-mursala?t verses 1-50, al-Naba? verses 1-40, al-Na?zi?a?t verses 1-46, ?abasa verses 1-42, al-takwi?r verses 1-29, al-infit?a?r verses 1-19, and al-mut?afifyn verses 1-16.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:35 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:29 ?????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ???? ?? ???????, ????? ??????? ??????, ????????, ???????? ???? ???? ??? ??? ???????. ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ,?????? ????? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ?? ???????
  ?? 0:00 ??? 28:00 ??? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ???????. ?????? ????? ???? ?? ??? ????? ??????? ?? ???????. ????? ?????? ???? ?? ??????? ???????. ????? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ??????? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??? ???? ?????, ?????? ??????, ?????? ???? ?????? ???????
  ?? 28:01 ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ???? ??????? ????? 24 ??? 31, ???????? ????? 1 ??? 50, ????? ????? 1 ??? 40, ???????? ????? 1 ??? 46, ??? ????? 1 ??? 42, ??????? ????? 1 ??? 29, ???????? ????? 1 ??? 19, ?????????? ????? 1 ??? 16
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 142. Q&A session on faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 142)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 47:03 min. Side B 46:39 min.
  0:00 to 1:22 recording is very faint and audio is unintelligible.